kuturl.com 2006-06-15

# KutURL.com :: - Make Your Long URL Shorter

|   
---  
|  KutURL.com Statement of Privacy  (last updated: September 2005)   NOTE:- KutURL.com is part of eProfitGroup. The following relates to all businesses and sites within the eProfitGroup network, including KutURL.com      We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully  We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.    We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent by either subscribing, enquiring or purchasing from us.   We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us or from another trader in the future.      The type of information we will collect about you includes:    your name  address  phone number  email address  credit/debit card details      We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.      The personal information which we hold will be held securely.    We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.      Use of Cookies eProfitGroup.com may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize eProfitGroup.com's pages, or register with eProfitGroup.com sites or services, a cookie helps eProfitGroup.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to eProfitGroup.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the eProfitGroup.com features that you customized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the eProfitGroup.com services or Web sites you visit.  A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.  You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information. in IE6, see eProfitGroup.com's Internet Explorer Web Privacy page.  in Netscape 6, see Netscape 6 - Safety with More Control.  in Opera 5 or 6, see Opera Preferences: Privacy.    Use of Web Beacons eProfitGroup.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow eProfitGroup.com to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. eProfitGroup.com may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or eProfitGroup.com Newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information on the eProfitGroup.com network of sites and services; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about eProfitGroup.com Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. eProfitGroup.com Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help determine the effectiveness of our Internet advertising campaigns.   Sharing Information Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. Personally Identifiable Information Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties.   eProfitGroup.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This eProfitGroup.com Statement of Privacy applies to eProfitGroup.com's eProfitGroup.com family of Web sites and governs data collection and usage at all eProfitGroup.com sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline eProfitGroup.com sites, products or services. Please read the eProfitGroup.com Statement of Privacy below and also any supplementary information at the end of this statement for additional details about particular eProfitGroup.com sites and services that you may use.   eProfitGroup.com is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.   Collection of your Personal Information At some sites, eProfitGroup.com collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. eProfitGroup.com may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. Information collected by eProfitGroup.com may be combined with information obtained from other eProfitGroup.com services and other companies. eProfitGroup.com also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by eProfitGroup.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of eProfitGroup.com.   eProfitGroup.com keeps track of the pages our customers visit within eProfitGroup.com, in order to determine what eProfitGroup.com sites and services are the most popular. This data is also used by eProfitGroup.com to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. eProfitGroup.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from eProfitGroup.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. eProfitGroup.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the eProfitGroup.com and eProfitGroup.com family of Web sites. Use of your Personal Information   eProfitGroup.com and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to operate eProfitGroup.com and deliver the services you have requested. eProfitGroup.com also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from eProfitGroup.com and its affiliates. eProfitGroup.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.   eProfitGroup.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. eProfitGroup.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.  We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.   eProfitGroup.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. eProfitGroup.com may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on eProfitGroup.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of eProfitGroup.com, including its eProfitGroup.com family of Web sites; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of eProfitGroup.com, its web sites, or the public. Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in any other country in which eProfitGroup.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.    You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from eProfitGroup.com by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. The instructions explain how to stop receiving such e-mails. There are some eProfitGroup.com services that send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues, product surveys, new feature announcements and news about eProfitGroup.com products and services. You will not be able to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered a part of the service you have chosen. Security of your Personal Information   eProfitGroup.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.   Use of Third Party Ad Networks The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on eProfitGroup.com Web pages are displayed by eProfitGroup.com. In addition, eProfitGroup.com may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on eProfitGroup.com Web pages. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. eProfitGroup.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.   Enforcement of this Statement of Privacy If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact eProfitGroup.com via e-mail.  Changes to this Statement eProfitGroup.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. When eProfitGroup.com posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of eProfitGroup.com. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how eProfitGroup.com will use your personal information, eProfitGroup.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. eProfitGroup.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how eProfitGroup.com is protecting your information. Contact Information eProfitGroup.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that eProfitGroup.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact eProfitGroup.com by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail.   eProfitGroup.com Privacy eProfitGroup.com 10 Millmount Charroterie St Peter Port Guernsey Channel Islands United Kingdom GY1 1EL     
|   
| 

**Check these out...**  

  * The  [ Business Professional](http://www.eprofitgroup.com/BusinessProfessional)
